#### KAHLIL IMMANUELLE BELLO

San Diego, CA 91911 | (442) 226-8470

bellos711@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

## **Technical Projects**

## Ecommerce Website - JavaScript, MongoDB, Express, React, Node (MERN)

An online store that incorporates a user management feature where an administrator can be assigned to handle user, products, and orders. Users are able to leave reviews on the products. React Redux is used on the client side for rendering pages and state management. MERN stack was a great choice due to its consistency with JavaScript.

### Web Scraper - C#, ASP.NET MVC, MySQL

Worked with a team of three to build a site that rated URL links based on external links scraped from the entered URL. The web application allows us to store keywords to the database for the app to parse through any known potentially malicious external links. The web application also incorporates a user login for Q&A.

## Sample Food Ordering Site - Python, Django, SQLite, HTML, CSS

A website that implements CRUD where a client can place an order and the administrator can receive, accept, and add menu items onto the site. The Django framework was used for its simplicity and extensive libraries.

### Blog Site with Content Management System - PHP, Apache, MySQL, HTML, CSS

A blog site that includes a content management system. Non-member users can view threads posted on the site and leave comments on posts which need approval. Administrators/moderators manage posts and approve pending comments with varying access levels. The blog posts themselves are separated via categories, and a search bar is included to navigate the site.

#### Mini Game Project - C#, Unity, Adobe Photoshop

A mini top-down arcade style game where targets appear in waves. Unity's game engine is used for having a 2D option for its workspace made it an ideal platform for development.

### **Technical Skills**

Programming Languages: C#, JavaScript, Python, C++, PHP, Java, HTML, CSS

**Databases:** MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite **Web Frameworks:** MERN, ASP.NET, Django

Development Tools: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Atom, Unity, Microsoft Office

### Work Experience

#### **United States Navy**

(December 2011 – December 2016)

# **Information Security Systems Officer**

(April 2015 – December 2016)

Maintained and updated hospital operating room department's site, scheduling system, and database by providing access to team members and collaborating with software developers in other departments. Provide both hardware and software related support through a ticketing system throughout the hospital facilitating over 1000 personnel.

Surgical Technician

(February 2013 – April 2015)

#### Education

University of La Verne, B.S. Computer Science, La Verne, CA

(August 2017 – June 2020)

Cumulative GPA: 3.60